R : What am I doing with my life ?
I 'm so pale . I should get out more .
I should eat better .
My posture is terrible . I should stand up straighter .
People would respect me more if I stood up straighter .
What 's wrong with me ? I just want to connect .
Why can 't I connect with people ?
Oh , right . It 's because I 'm dead .
I shouldn 't be so hard on myself . I mean , we 're all dead .
This girl is dead . That guy 's dead .
That guy in the corner is definitely dead .
- Jesus , these guys look awful . ( ZOMBIES MOANING )
I wish I could introduce myself ,
but I don 't remember my name anymore .
I mean , I think it started with an " R " , but that 's all I have left .
I can 't remember my name , or my parents , or my job .
Although my hoodie would suggest I was unemployed .
( SCANNER BEEPS )
Sometimes I look at the others and try to imagine what they were .
You were a janitor .
You were the rich son of a corporate CEO .
You were a personal trainer .
( SCREAMING ) ( BALL BOUNCING )
And now you 're a Corpse .
I have a hard time piecing together how this whole apocalypse thing happened .
Could have been chemical warfare or an airborne virus ,
or a radioactive outbreak monkey .
But it doesn 't really matter . This is what we are now .
This is a typical day for me .
I shuffle around occasionally bumping into people ,
unable to apologize or say much of anything .
It must have been so much better before ,
when everyone could express themselves ,
and communicate their feelings
and just enjoy each other 's company .
A lot of us have made our home here at this airport .
I don 't know why .
People wait at airports , I guess ,
but I 'm not sure what we 're all waiting for .
( BONEYS GROWLING )
Oh , man . They call these guys Boneys .
They don 't bother us much .
But they 'll eat anything with a heartbeat .
I mean , I will too , but at least I 'm conflicted about it .
We all become them some day .
At some point you just give up , I guess .
You lose all hope . After that , there 's no turning back .
Oh , man , gross .
Stop . Stop , don 't pick at it ! You 're making it worse !
Oh , this is what I have to look forward to .
It 's kind of a bummer .
I don 't want to be this way .
I 'm lonely . I 'm lost .
I mean , I 'm literally lost .
I 've never been in this part of the airport before .
Wonder if these guys are lost , too .
Wandering around but never getting anywhere .
Do they feel trapped ? Do they want more than this ?
Am I the only one ?
( SONG PLAYING )
R : This is my best friend .
( M GROANING )
By best friend , I mean we occasionally grunt
and stare awkwardly at each other .
( BOTH GRUNT )
We even have almost-conversations sometimes .
( BOTH GRUNTING RHYTHMICALLY )
Days pass this way .
But sometimes we even find actual words . Words like ...
Hungry .
And ...
City .
Uh .
Even though we can 't communicate
we do share a similar taste in food .
Traveling in packs just kind of makes sense ,
especially when everyone and their grandmother
is trying to shoot you in the head all the time .
God , we move slow .
( SIGHS ) This could take a while .
( INDISTINCT TALKING )
Hello , and thank you for your Service today .
In the eight years since this plague destroyed our world ...
You think we 're getting this stuff for the cure ?
... since we erected this wall ...
No one believes in a cure anymore , Jules .
... we have counted on young volunteers like you
to gather resources from beyond the wall .
But first , a Word of caution .
Corpses look human , they are not .
They do not think . They do not bleed .
Whether they were your mother or your best friend ,
they are beyond your help .
They are uncaring , unfeeling , incapable of remorse .
Sound like anyone you know , Dad ?
Just picture them as this .
( GROWLING )
As sons and daughters of possibly the sole remaining
human settlement on Earth ,
you are a critical part
of what stands between us and extinction .
Therefore you have an obligation to return to us safely .
And if you remember your training , you will .
Good luck , Godspeed ‚ and God bless America .
USA ! USA !
PERRY : Let 's go .
( ALARM RINGING )
Sweet .
( SOFT MUSIC PLAYING )
( INHALES DEEPLY )
( GUN FIRING )
Hey , Berg , you gonna help us out or what ?
- No dice . Almost at level five . ( LOW SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE )
( HEAVY THUD IN DISTANCE )
Did you hear that ?
I did . We should bail .
Oh , hey , we can 't just bail . We have orders .
Do you have any idea how much medicine the City goes through a month ?
We need pharma salvage to survive .
- We can 't just abandon our ... - You sound just like my dad .
- Thank you . - Yeah , it wasn 't a compliment .
Oh , here , guys . Take some Prozac .
Maybe that will cheer you up .
( METAL CLANKS )
I told you I heard something .
( COCKING GUN )
Per , let 's bail .
Perry ?
We have orders , Jules .
It was nothing anyway .
- You 're being paranoid , okay ? - Perry !
( GROWLING )
( GUNS FIRING )
Aim for their heads !
( GRUNTING )
( GROWLS )
Smile , mother ...
( SCREAMS )
( GRUNTING )
R : - Nice watch . ( SCREAMING )
Now , I 'm not proud of this .
In fact , I 'd appreciate it
if you might look away for a moment here .
I don 't like hurting people ‚ but this is the world now .
The new hunger is a very powerful thing .
( GROANS )
If I don 't eat all of him , if I spare his brain ,
he 'll rise up and become a Corpse like me .
But if I do , I get his memories ,
his thoughts , his feelings .
I 'm sorry , I just can 't help it .
The brain 's the best part .
The part that makes me feel human again .
( IMITATES EXPLOSION )
You like it , Perry ?
R : I don 't want to hurt you .
I just want to feel what you felt .
To feel a little better .
A little less dead .
Perry ... I think I love you .
Say something .
Don 't just say nothing .
No , I , um ...
I think I love you too , Julie .
I miss airplanes .
My mom used to say that it looked like
an Etch A Sketch up there .
I like that you remember that kind of stuff .
If we don 't , then it will just all be gone . You know ?
Yeah .
The world is so messed up .
Not all of it .
Cheeseball .
( BOTH CHUCKLE )
Perry ?
( ZOMBIES GROWLING )
- Perry ! ( MACHINE GUN FIRING )
Perry , where are you ? Answer me !
( GROWLS )
( CLATTERING )
( R GROWLS )
( STAMMERING ) Julie ...
J ... Julie ...
( SNIFFING )
Safe .
Come ...
What ?
R : I don 't know what I 'm doing . What 's wrong with me ?
These other guys would never bring a living person home .
You know why ? Because that 's crazy !
Right now , they think she 's just another one of us .
A new addition to the family .
But they would think I was insane .
If they could think .
Why do I have to be so weird ?
What am I doing ?
( SCANNER BEEPS )
( WIND WHISTLING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( SOBBING )
Home ...
( SOBS )
( STAMMERING ) Not eat .
Keep you safe .
( GASPS )
( DOOR CLOSES )
All right .
Maybe I could have thought this through a little more .
But I can tell when a girl needs her space .
There 's a lot of ways to get to know a person .
Eating her dead boyfriend 's brains
is one of the more unorthodox methods , but ...
( CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING )
GRIGIO : It 's a special occasion .
A special occasion , sir ?
It 's Mom 's birthday .
- To Diane . - To Mom .
Yeah .
- It 's Mom 's birthday . GRIGIO : - So , Perry ,
Julie tells me you 've been working in Agriculture .
But tell me you would never consider
going to work construction with your father .
You know , on the wall we need good people .
Um ...
Don 't mind him , Per . Dad 's idea of saving humanity
is to build a really big concrete box , put everyone in it ,
and then wait at the door with guns until we grow old and die .
Well , Julie , without the wall , we would be eating brains now
- instead of rice . - Dad ...
JULIE : This is the only way past the wall .
Otherwise we get stopped .
Okay ...
Come on . It 's not that bad . Come on .
I haven 't heard from him in two days , Jules .
He 's on construction detail , Perry . He 's working .
My dad goes weeks without checking in .
Okay . This way .
Hey .
It 's gonna be okay .
( COMMENTARY PLAYING FAINTLY )
( HITTING BALL )
( CROWD CHEERING )
Dad .
Per .
( GROWLS )
Whoa , whoa , hey , hey , hey !
Perry ! Come on !
R : No wonder she 's so afraid of me .
I need a different approach .
Okay , here we go . Don 't be creepy .
Don 't be creepy . Don 't be creepy .
( SHIVERING )
What are you doing ?
Please leave me alone .
Why me ?
Why did you save me ?
Don 't
c ... cry .
( SOFT MUSIC PLAYING )
Safe .
Keep you safe .
What are you ?
( SIGHS )
I 'm hungry .
Just let me go !
( STAMMERING ) Not safe .
Not safe ?
Uh-huh . Not safe .
( JULIE SIGHS )
Well , then you 're just gonna have to go and get me some food .
Because I 'm starved .
Please ?
I 'd be very grateful for some food .
O ... okay .
( DOOR CLOSES )
( ZOMBIE GROANS )
God !
( ZOMBIES SNIFFING )
Shit .
( GASPS )
Don 't r ... run .
( SNIFFING )
Come . S ... safe .
Thank you .
( ZOMBIES GROANING )
Be dead .
( GROANING )
Okay ?
( GRUNTING )
That 's too m ... much .
Told you not s ... safe .
Yeah , I get that .
I really am hungry , though .
JULIE : Yes !
Mmm .
My God .
Oh , no . Stop staring . You 're acting weird again .
( RATTLING )
Thank you .
Oh , my God .
Mmm !
Oh , man .
I can 't remember the last time I had a beer .
I guess you can 't be all that bad , Mr. Zombie .
( STAMMERING ) My name ...
You have a name ?
What is your name ?
Rrrrrrrrrrr ..
Rrrr ?
R : This date is not going well .
I want to die all over again .
Rrrrrrr ...
Does your name start with " R " ?
Um ...
Robert ? Richard ?
Randy ?
Raphael ? Ricardo ?
Why don 't I just call you " R " ?
I mean , that 's a start , right ?
R ...
I want to go home , R.
Mmm-mmm .
It 's n-not safe .
I get that .
And look ...
I know that you saved my life .
And I 'm grateful for that .
But you walked me into this place .
So I know that you can walk me out again .
Oh , no . She can 't leave . She just got here .
Tell her she has to wait . Tell her they 'll notice .
H ... h ... have to wait .
They ... They 'll notice .
Huh . Not bad .
How long ?
F ... f ... few d ... days .
Th ... they 'll f ... forget .
Y ... y ... you 'll be o-kay .
Are there others like you ?
I mean , I 've ...
I 've never ever heard a Corpse talk before .
I mean , apart from the groaning .
Okay . A few days , huh ?
What am I supposed to do for a few days around here anyway ?
This is awesome !
You wanna try ?
Oh , God !
Oh ! You 're a leadfoot .
Okay . Okay . Pick a foot .
You 're using two feet . Pick one foot ...
There you go . Okay ...
( LAUGHS )
There you go .
All right . Two hands on the wheel , buddy .
( JULIE GRUNTS )
Jesus , R !
This was a beautiful car !
AUTOMATED VOICE : Recalculating .
( SCOFFS )
( BREATHES DEEPLY )
What 's with all the vinyl ?
Couldn 't figure out how to work an iPod ?
Better s ... sound .
Oh , you 're a purist , huh ?
More
alive .
Yeah . That 's true . Lot more trouble , though .
There you go again . Shrugging .
Stop shrugging , shrugger .
It 's a very non-committal gesture .
Really ?
These are really cool records . How did you get all these ?
I collect things .
Yeah , I can see that . You , my friend , are a hoarder .
Man , there 's this awesome record store on Main and Ivy .
You would love it . It 's so cool .
Was so cool .
Alrighty .
( SONG PLAYING )
Much better .
R ? Can I ask you something ?
My boyfriend , he died back there .
Will he come back ? As one of you ?
( SIGHS )
That 's good , I guess .
Something happened to him .
A lot of things happened to him .
But I guess there just came a point where
he couldn 't absorb any more .
It 's just , in my world , people die all the time .
So ... You know , it 's not like
I 'm not sad that he 's gone .
Because I am .
But I think I 've been
preparing for it for a really long time .
( SONG PLAYING )
What are you ?
R : Man , it must be nice to sleep . I wish I could .
I wish I could dream .
But that 's not really an option for me .
The dead don 't dream . This is as close as we get .
You sure about this , son ?
Welcome , then .
Sorry for your loss .
Me , too .
Give him one and show him how to use it .
Hey , Berg , you gonna help us out or what ?
I 'm almost at level five .
( HEAVY THUD IN DISTANCE )
Did you hear that ?
I did . We should bail .
PERRY : We can 't just bail . We have orders .
You sound just like my dad .
- Thank you . - Yeah , it wasn 't a compliment .
I told you I heard something .
JULIE : Perry !
Aim for their heads .
( SPITTING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( JULIE SCREAMING )
( WEED WHACKER WHIRRING )
( GROWLS )
( GRUNTING )
( SNIFFING )
( JULIE SCREAMS )
You said a few days . It 's been a few days , R.
I have to go home .
S ... stay t ... together .
Safe .
( M GROWLING )
What ?
J ... Julie .
Living .
Eat !
( LOW GROWLING )
Oh , my God !
We go .
Eat .
R. Look .
( ZOMBIES MOANING )
( GROWLING )
( ROARS )
( BANGING ON DOOR )
This way .
Come with me .
What ?
No !
Want to help her .
Who the hell asked you ?
Like her .
It 's okay .
I 'm sure it is .
- Over there , the garage . - Hold on .
( SIGHS ) I 'm so happy to see you right now .
You okay ?
Um ... R ?
( ZOMBIES SNIFFING AND MOANING )
You drive .
Good idea .
( ENGINE STARTS )
( BONEY SHRIEKS )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( ROARING )
MALE VOICE ON PA : The White zone
is for loading and unloading of passengers only .
( SONG PLAYING )
Jesus , I 'm freezing .
I have to pull over .
This is one of the last neighborhoods my dad evacuated .
Maybe these houses have food .
Okay , come on .
( RATTLING DOOR ) - Oh , man . It 's locked .
( THUDS )
Oh , God .
( JULIE SHIVERING )
Oh , cool !
Look what they have .
I haven 't seen one of these in forever .
Cheese !
( CHUCKLES )
It 's all right . See ?
Yeah .
It 's important to preserve memories , you know ?
Especially now that the world is on its way out .
Everything you see , you may be seeing for the last time .
Perry used to say that .
Here . Take a picture .
( FOOTSTEPS )
( JULIE SIGHS )
I 'm exhausted .
The bed actually isn 't too rotten , so I 'm gonna go to sleep .
Good night .
Um ...
R ?
Y ... yeah ?
I was ... I was thinking ...
You know , you could sleep in there if you want .
On the floor .
These houses creep me out , so ...
Okay .
( M BREATHING HEAVILY )
( ZOMBIES MOANING )
Do you feel it ?
( HEARTS BEATING )
( NECK CRACKS )
( BONEYS GROWLING )
( SNIFFING )
( ROARS )
( SHUSHING )
SOLDIER : Hey , look up this street .
Holy shit . That 's my dad .
Get back !
He would have killed you .
If he saw you , he would have just shot you in the head ,
and you 'd just be gone .
( EXHALES )
These clothes are soaking still .
I 'm gonna lay them out to dry .
Oh , relax .
R : Holy shit .
Don 't look .
Okay .
Holy shit !
Hey .
Do you have to eat people ?
Y ... yeah .
Or you 'll die ?
- Yeah . - But you didn 't eat me .
You rescued me . Like , a bunch .
It must be hard being stuck in there .
You know , I can see you trying .
Maybe that 's what people do .
You know , we try to be better .
Sometimes we kind of suck at it .
But I look at you and
you try so much harder than any human in my city .
You 're a good person , R.
Anyway .
It was me .
What was you ?
( TICKING )
Oh .
I mean , I ...
I guess I kind of knew that .
Y ... you did ?
Yeah , I ...
I guess I hoped that you didn 't .
I 'm sorry .
Julie ...
I 'm so s-sorry .
R : The dead do not sleep .
( BIRDS TWITTERING )
JULIE : If you guys could pick any job in the world ...
Pretend that everything was totally different ,
what would you want to do ?
- Nursing . - Yeah ?
Yeah . Healing people and
saving lives and ...
I don 't know , finding a cure .
I like that .
I think someday someone 's gonna figure out this whole thing and
exhume the whole world .
Exhume ? And what does that mean ?
Um , exhume means to , like , revive .
It means to dig up . As in digging up a corpse .
Whatever .
What the hell are you doing here ?
Are you actually dreaming right now ?
I 'm not sure .
You can 't dream , Corpse . Dreaming is for humans .
Chill out , Per . He can dream if he wants to .
What about you , R ?
What do you want to be ?
I don 't know . I don 't even know what I am .
Well , you can be whatever you want .
Isn 't that what they say ?
We can , right ? You and me ?
Mmm-hmm .
It 's not gonna happen , loverboy .
Not after you told her you ate her ex .
Shrug .
( SONG PLAYING )
R : So much for dreaming .
You can 't be whatever you want .
All I 'll ever be is a slow , pale ,
hunched-over , dead-eyed zombie .
What did I think was gonna happen ?
That she 'd actually want to stay with me ?
It 's hopeless . This is what I get for wanting more .
I should just be happy with what I had .
Things don 't change . I need to accept that .
It 's easier not to feel .
Then I wouldn 't have to feel like this .
I 've been alone too many nights
Too proud to tell you when you 're right
A little patience would have helped me then
A lot like the break has been the common Standard
All the angels above the earth I prayed
Send this message right into her head
There 's certain things in life I cannot take
And I Will Wait
I hope you know I care
So cold I know you can 't believe it
Sometimes you gotta face the feeling
When you don 't care if you get up again
There 's a thousand things I will not understand
I hope you know I care
Now you 're dealing with the hell I put you through
If I had my way I would be right there next to you
There 's certain things in life you cannot change
There 's certain things
Identify yourself !
It 's just me , Kevin . It 's okay . I 'm fine .
Just stop right there .
It 's okay . I 'm not infected .
I said stop , Julie !
Okay . Fine . Fine .
Let me check you out .
( DEVICE BEEPING )
- Is she okay ? - Clear , sir .
Hi , Dad .
I sent a half a dozen units out looking for you .
Nora said you were taken into ...
Yeah , I was . But I escaped .
I was holed up in a house in the suburbs
and then I found a car , so I came here .
Julie , are you sure nothing bit you ?
Do I look infected to you , Dad ?
We have to be safe .
Yeah , I know . I know .
I 'm fine , though . I promise .
I thought I lost you .
Well , you didn 't , Dad . I 'm here .
Welcome home .
Yeah . Good to be back .
So I 'm just gonna go home . I 'm gonna blend in .
I 'm gonna stop thinking so much .
I 'm gonna forget about her ,
just like I forgot about everything else .
I 'm gonna ... Oh , shit , am I cold ?
Is that what this is ? Corpses don 't get cold .
M : Yo !
What are you doing here ?
Boneys . They chased me out .
Came to find you .
Where is she ?
Went home .
You okay ?
No .
Bitches , man .
Boneys looking for you .
And her .
You started something .
I saw
pictures
last night .
Memories .
My mom ...
Summertime .
Cream
of Wheat .
A girl .
A dream ?
A dream .
We are changing , I think .
We are .
I ... I have to tell her .
W ... will you help ?
H ... help ?
Ex-hume ?
ZOMBIE : E-exhume .
( ZOMBIES GROANING IN AGREEMENT )
They said
" Fuck , yeah ! "
Wait here .
Be careful . Okay ?
So I 'll wait here .
It 's not that bad . Come on .
R : Julie and I were giving the others hope .
And it was spreading fast .
I guess the Boneys didn 't like that .
That must be why they 're looking for us .
I have to tell Julie .
I have to explain what 's happening before it 's too late . I have to ...
Oh , no . Oh , no . Please , go !
Go with your friends ! Shoo ! Leave me !
That 's it ! Okay .
No , I 'm serious , Nora . I mean , " Corpse " is just ...
It 's just a stupid name that we came up with
for a state of being that we don 't understand .
Yeah .
( SIGHS ) Oh , my God !
What is wrong with me ?
Okay .
I 've got to tell you something .
This is kind of weird .
- Please do not freak out . - No .
But I actually miss him .
- You ... You miss him ? - I know , it 's so stupid .
- Like you 're attracted to him ? - No , I don 't ...
Like he could be your boyfriend ?
Your zombie boyfriend ?
I mean , I know it 's really hard to meet guys right now
with the apocalypse and stuff , trust me .
And look , I know that you miss Perry .
Okay ? But , Julie , this is weird .
Like , I wish the Internet was still working so I could just look up
whatever it is that 's wrong with you .
Shut up .
All right .
Okay . I 'm getting ready for bed .
Hey .
( JULIE SIGHS )
I 'm glad you 're back .
Yeah .
( SING-SONG ) Have sweet dreams about your zombie .
All right . ( CHUCKLES )
( SIGHS )
Julie .
Julie !
Oh , my God .
R !
What are you doing here ?
Came to see you .
R ...
You can 't just do that . It 's dangerous .
NORA : Grigio , shut up ! I 'm trying to sleep !
Uh , sorry !
Jesus , R , are you crazy ?
The people here , they 're not like me .
If they see you , you 'll get killed .
Do you understand that ?
Yes .
NORA : Are you talking to yourself ?
- No ! ( DOOR OPENS )
NORA : Okay , seriously , what is going on out here , Julie ?
Oh , my God ! Is that him ?
Yeah .
'Sup ?
I 'm sorry .
I know . I 'm sorry , too .
I actually missed you .
Me , too .
It 's funny . You feel warmer than I remember .
( SIREN WAILING )
That 's the patrol . Come on , we better get you inside .
( JULIE SIGHS )
Come on .
You 're lucky my dad got pulled into some emergency thing .
You 're safe here tonight , R.
After that , I don 't know what we 're gonna do .
How did you die ?
I don 't remember .
How old are you ?
Because you could be twenty-something , but you could also be a teenager .
- You have one of those faces . - Oh , my God .
And I can 't even smell ... You don 't smell ...
He doesn 't smell rotten .
- I don 't ... - Amazing .
Nora , he didn 't come here for an interview . Stop .
Why did you come here , R ?
To show everyone ...
Show them what ?
That we can change .
R , no one here is ever gonna buy that .
Not that we could get you even close enough to tell them .
As soon as they saw you , they would blow your head to bits .
Wait a minute . Did you say " we " ?
Lots of us changing .
Dreaming .
That 's kind of a big deal .
We have to move fast .
What do you mean ?
Boneys chasing me . They 're chasing us .
Okay , we have to go to my dad .
No , that is a very bad idea .
No , Nora , he was a reasonable guy once .
( CHUCKLES ) Oh , no , I think you 're confused .
It was your mom that was the reasonable one .
It was your dad that grounded you for a year for stealing Peach Schnapps .
Are you serious ? It 's your dad that likes to shoot Corpses in the head .
Well , what other choice do we have , Nora ?
( SIGHS ) Still , we 'd have to get him through the city .
Someone would definitely see you .
There isn 't much time .
We could fix him up .
What ?
I have some makeup that I was saving for a special occasion
that obviously isn 't gonna happen .
Yeah . Yeah , we could .
We could put on a little bit of foundation ,
maybe a little blush . Probably a lot of blush .
No way .
Yeah , way .
( OH PRETTY WOMAN PLAYING )
Would you change the song , please ?
What ? It 's funny .
No , it 's not .
Fine .
( SONG PLAYING )
There we go .
Oh , yeah .
Hold up ...
You look hot !
( COCKING GUN )
( GROWLING )
( BONEYS ROARING )
What ?
Nothing .
It 's just , you look nice .
I don 't know how my dad 's gonna be .
He gets kind of crazy . This might not work .
Hey .
No matter what , we stay together .
We 're changing everything .
I know .
Stay together . Promise .
I promise .
Come on .
Hey , it 's game time . All right , let 's do this .
KEVIN : Excuse me .
Where are you guys headed ?
To see my dad , Kevin .
Miss Grigio , I can 't let you guys in .
We 're on high alert around here .
- Why ? What 's going on ? - It 's classified .
All right , well , we have our own classified business ,
So come on .
Hey .
R : Say something human . Say something human .
How are you ?
Nailed it .
Over here . He 's fine .
Okay , you guys wait here .
What are you doing here ?
What is going on ? What is all this ?
I 'm not sure , but it 's not good .
We 've been getting reports
there are sizable packs of skeletons and Corpses
coming toward us .
We don 't know why , but if they 're here to attack ,
there 's nothing we can do about it .
Too many of them , too few of us .
So I want you to get home , lock down the house .
I have the gun there , the Ruger SR ...
This ? Yeah , okay . I need to talk to you .
- Julie , not now . - Dad , it 's important .
This is gonna sound really crazy , but
I think the dead are coming back to life .
That does sound crazy .
They 're changing , Dad . They 're ...
I don 't know . They 're somehow curing themselves .
You think they 're curing themselves ? How is that ?
I saw it . It is really happening .
No . You know what is happening , Julie ?
What 's happening is every day there are more of them and less of us .
They are not curing themselves .
We 're their food source .
They are not becoming vegan . Okay ? They don 't eat broccoli .
They eat brains , your mother 's and your boyfriend 's included .
Okay ? So I want you to wake up !
- I 'll explain . GRIGIO : - Okay ?
What do you mean , " you 'll explain " ? Explain what ?
I got this .
Get yourself home .
Barricade yourself in the shelter .
There is enough stuff there that you can open up ...
Uh ... Hi .
Who are you ?
This is R.
I didn 't ask you . I asked him . Who are you ?
( STAMMERING )
You 're a Corpse ?
He saved my life .
He took care of me .
I triggered something in him
and that must have sparked something in all of them ...
- Now it 's triggered something in me . JULIE : - No ...
Dad ! No ! Dad !
We want to help .
Please , they don 't want to attack us . They want to help .
We 're ... We 're getting better .
No . Things don 't get better . Things get worse .
People get bit , then they get infected , then I shoot them in the head .
- No , Dad ... - That 's what happened
to your mother , and that 's what 's gonna happen to him .
( GUN COCKING )
I 'm really sorry , Mr. Grigio .
Go . Get out of here and be safe , no matter what . Okay ?
Julie ...
I have to go .
You 're not gonna shoot me .
Yes . Yeah , I will . Totally .
( PANTING )
Okay . That could have gone better .
I need to warn my friends .
- Where ? - The stadium ...
( ALARM BLARING )
Shit ! Come on ! Get on the subway !
( GASPS )
Whoa .
M : Excuse me . Excuse me . Sorry .
Coming through .
R.
Julie .
Hi .
Ready for a fight .
Yeah , I can see that .
R : S-soldiers coming . Boneys closing in .
( BONEYS GROWLING )
( THUDDING )
( GLASS SHATTERING )
They 're here now .
- Keep them out . - We will .
Run .
( ALL SHRIEKING )
( SOLDIERS SHOUTING )
JULIE : This way , come on !
SOLDIER : Sir , your daughter is with the Corpse .
I 've got eyes on them .
( ROARS )
( GRUNTING )
( ALL CLAMORING )
( GROWLS ) ( JULIE GASPS )
( SCREAMS )
Thank you .
Who the hell do we shoot ?
This asshole .
Hi .
Hey . Hi . Hi .
SOLDIER 1 : We see Corpses fighting skeletons , sir .
SOLDIER 2 : Copy that . We 're Seeing that over here , too .
Sorry , can you repeat that ?
Copy that . We 're seeing Corpses fighting skeletons , sir .
JULIE : Shit !
( BONEY GROWLING )
It 's over .
No . Keep you safe .
It will be okay .
R ?
R !
R , please ?
You Okay ?
- Yeah . - Yeah ?
Whoa .
( GUN FIRES )
( GASPS )
Next one 's the head . Move away from him , Julie .
JULIE : No !
Julie , move now .
Dad , you have to listen to me .
I know we lost everybody .
I know you lost Mom . But you and me , we are still here .
We can fix all this . We can start over .
They need our help .
Please , Dad ! Look at him .
He 's different . He 's ...
Bleeding .
He 's bleeding , Dad .
Corpses don 't bleed !
Oh , God .
You 're alive . He 's alive !
( JULIE LAUGHS )
You 're alive .
Does it hurt ?
Yeah .
Yeah ?
Sir ?
This is Colonel Grigio . The situation has changed .
Let 's get you two the hell out of here .
Are you still bleeding ?
- Yes . - Good .
Sorry .
R : On the one hand , getting shot in the chest hurt .
Like , a lot .
But on the other , it felt good to bleed , to feel pain .
To feel love .
I wish I could say we cured the Boneys with love ,
but really , we just straight up killed them all .
It sounds kind of messed up , but no one felt too bad about it .
They were too far gone to change .
It was actually a really good bonding experience for us and the humans .
Once we joined forces , they didn 't stand a Chance .
The ones we didn 't kill just wasted away .
And the rest of us ?
Weil , we kind of learned how to live again .
For a while , it seemed like a lot of us forgot what that meant .
The humans began to accept us , connect with us , teach us .
This was the key to the cure .
It was scary at first , but
every great thing starts out a little scaly , doesn 't it ?
This is how it happened .
This is how the world was
exhumed .
You need some help ?
Yeah .
I have , uh , zombie fingers .
Thank you .
Here .
Oh , it 's okay . I don 't mind the rain .
I insist .
I 'm ...
Mar-marcus .
Emily .
You 're ... You 're very pretty .
Thank you , Marcus .
Now you 're supposed to say I 'm pretty , too .
R ?
Yeah ?
Do you remember your name yet ?
No .
Well , you know , you could just give yourself one .
Just pick one . Whatever you want .
I like " R. "
Really ?
You don 't want to know what it was ?
You don 't want your old life back ?
No .
I want this one .
( SIGHS )
Just " R , " huh ?
Just " R. "